<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Asineth</title>
    <link>https://asineth.me/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Asineth</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://asineth.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Having School on Festivus is Evil</title>
      <link>https://asineth.me/festivus-school/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2020 20:27:47 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://asineth.me/festivus-school/</guid>
      <description>Look at this young boy being oppressed during Festivus.
 The issue In many public schools across the United States, children are being forced against their will, to attend school on the day of Festivus. This is a tragic event, that so many students&#39; holiday traditions on Festivus are being impeded and oppressed by the public school system. They&amp;rsquo;re fine with giving these same children Christmas off, so they can go consume and purchase commerical goods, but they don&amp;rsquo;t want them to celebrate Festivus, they don&amp;rsquo;t want them questioning the holiday they&amp;rsquo;re told to celebrate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unofficial ROMs for Moto G8/G8 Power</title>
      <link>https://asineth.me/android-rav/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://asineth.me/android-rav/</guid>
      <description>Status Both ROMs are currently very stable and I&amp;rsquo;ve used them for multiple hours with minimal or no issues. I may port Bliss or some other ROMs later.
Downloads Last updated: 2020.09.17 @ 21:55 EDT
 lineage-17.1-20200918-UNOFFICIAL-sofiar.zip MEGA pCloud  SHA256: ba7445fbadada6edbe12b55ecfce0d4bd2a7ca1b407a5f0a44a42b8e2eb27e99
 PixelExperience_Plus_sofiar-10.0-20200918-0058-UNOFFICIAL.zip MEGA pCloud  SHA256: 6e6a3f050e3bf8227abf5d46a616d772515884d1c2b6256777f51518158877cb
Flashing  Unlock bootloader  You can unlock your bootloader at Motorola&amp;rsquo;s website.
Boot into fastbootd  Reboot your device into the bootloader by holding power + volume down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using an Android as a SBC/Pi alternative</title>
      <link>https://asineth.me/phone-server/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://asineth.me/phone-server/</guid>
      <description>Motivation I have old Android phones lying around and wanted to host a Minecraft server for friends. I initially thought of buying an SBC such as Pi or ODROID, instead I though to try and use an old phone instead.
How My setup works by configuring an SSH server, a chroot with a Linux distro that supports aarch64, and configuring init scripts so that Android&amp;rsquo;s system UI gets stopped and doesn&amp;rsquo;t take up resources.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Debian 10 Root on Encrypted ZFS</title>
      <link>https://asineth.me/debian-zfs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://asineth.me/debian-zfs/</guid>
      <description>Motivation Why would you want to use ZFS as your root filesystem?
 Snapshots and rollbacks Send incremental snapshots over the network Datasets (i.e. /home, /var, /tmp) Copy-on-write architecture Compression to save space Checksums for data integrity, auto-repair Built-in native encryption Flexible configuration per dataset  Context ZFS is awesome, why isn&amp;rsquo;t it the default filesystem? Well, it mainly stems from one thing, and that&amp;rsquo;s licensing. ZFS is licensed under the CDDL, and the Linux kenrel is licensed under the GPL.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Booting a GSI on the Pixel 1/1 XL</title>
      <link>https://asineth.me/pixel-gsi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://asineth.me/pixel-gsi/</guid>
      <description>Requirements  Google Pixel 1/1 XL (sailfish/marlin) A GSI system.img to flash ADB &amp;amp; Fastboot on your PC TWRP for your device  Getting a GSI There are tons of different GSIs to try out. I used the Google one.
 Google&amp;rsquo;s Android 10 GSI Google&amp;rsquo;s Android 11 GSI phhTreble Android 10 phhTreble Android 10 + GApps phhTreble Android 10 + &amp;ldquo;Go&amp;rdquo; Gapps  Preparing the device The system_a and system_b partitions on the Pixel are too small for the GSI.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
